<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chromer</string>
    <string name="custom_tab_provider_not_found">Compatible custom tab provider not found</string>
    <string name="custom_tab_provider_not_found_expln">Chromer requires you to have any Custom tab compatible browser on your phone. Currently there are no browsers on your phone that supports it. Would you like to install Google Chrome (Free) from play store? If you already have it, then please update it to latest version.</string>
    <string name="install">Install</string>
    <string name="choose_default_provider">Choose default provider</string>
    <string name="fallback_msg">Could not open custom tab, falling back to normal browsers</string>
    <string name="open_with">Open with…</string>
    <string name="unxp_err">Unexpected error, try again</string>
    <string name="unsupported_link">Not a supported link, try again</string>
    <string name="default_pref_xpln">Set Chromer as default to open all links, or you can choose Chromer from the list when it is shown</string>
    <string name="default_clear_msg">is set as the default browser, please clear it by clicking clear defaults.</string>
    <string name="keep_chrome_warmedup">Keep your browser warmed up for faster launch</string>
    <string name="warmup_browser">Warm up browser</string>
    <string name="set_default_chromer">Set Default Browser</string>
    <string name="default_provider">Choose default provider</string>
    <string name="pre_fetch_content">Prefetch content</string>
    <string name="pre_fetch_desc">Scan your screen for links and load them in background for instant launch</string>
    <string name="accesiblity_description">This service will be used by Chromer to scan text links on your screen and load them in the background. No other information is processed by Chromer. You can still use Chromer in light mode if you choose to not grant this. For more information, launch Chromer app.</string>
    <string name="accesiblity_dialog_title">Accessibility permission required</string>
    <string name="accesiblity_dialog_desc">To allow Chromer to scan for links in any app, it requires you to grant accessibility service permission. Please grant accessibility permission in the next screen, after which you can enable this option and enjoy quick launches.</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Open Settings</string>
    <string name="only_on_wifi">Only on Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="choose_secondary_browser">Choose secondary browser</string>
    <string name="licenses">Licenses</string>
</resources>
